MARWAN GRADA

UX/UI Designer

PROFILE

I like to call myself a "Problem Solver" as that is what UX design means to me - finding solutions to problems using a design-centric approach. With a background in business and a Masters degree in Education and Cognitive Psychology, I work at the intersection of humans and technology to design products that listen to the users' needs.

I love creating aesthetically pleasing, functional web products with rock-solid code. Turning complex problems into simple beautiful and intuitive interface designs with more than 4 years experience, from brainstorms and wireframes, to prototypes and production-ready assets. Apply user-centered design and design thinking in order to connect customer needs with business objectives. My toolkit includes Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (React.js, JQuery, Node.js) Bootstrap and Wordpress.

CONTACT

PHONE

347-666-4317

EMAIL

grada.luck@gmail.com

WEBSITE

www.marwangrada.com

fm

EXPERIENCE

2013 - Present Front End Developer / Web Designer

GIA (Gemological Institute of America)

Web Content Specialist (Jan 2017 - Present)

FINLANDIA VODKA

UX Designer/Graphic Designer (May - Jul 2015)

STORY WORLDWIDE

Web Designer (Oct 2014 - Aug 2015)

ATMI JR

Front-End Developer/Graphic Designer (Jul - Sep 2016)

Jr.Print Designer (Oct 2014 - Jan 2015)

EDUCATION

2015 - 2016 New York Code + Design Academy

Web Development/ UX Design Certification

2014 - 2016 Touro College NYC

Masters in Education - TESOL

2004 - 2009 **University of Tripoli**

Bachelors in Business Administration

SKILLS

Wordpress

TECHNICAL SKILLS SOFT SKILLS

HTML5 Critical thinking CSS3 Adaptability Javascript Negotiation Photoshop Communication Illustrator Problem solving Indesign **Emotional Intelligence** Adobe XD Commitment Organization